<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Lapjo</title>
    <link>https://lapjo.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Lapjo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lapjo.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fucked up my mental</title>
      <link>https://lapjo.com/posts/stuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 01:36:25 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lapjo.com/posts/stuck/</guid>
      <description>Life can sometimes deal us an unfavorable hand, and it&amp;rsquo;s during these times that we must choose to confront our circumstances head-on or risk falling into a cycle of regret. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently faced a period of stagnation, which led to feelings of uncertainty and inaction. However, I&amp;rsquo;ve come to realize that taking a step back to reevaluate and strategize is essential for personal growth.&#xA;In my journey, I&amp;rsquo;ve neglected responsibilities, such as not completing two certificate exams I&amp;rsquo;ve paid for and neglecting my businesses and family time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix i3 window manager error &#39;No Polkit Authentication Agent&#39;</title>
      <link>https://lapjo.com/posts/no-polkit-authentication-agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 16:04:20 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lapjo.com/posts/no-polkit-authentication-agent/</guid>
      <description>A little introduction So, I recently switched to i3wm and ran into a small issue with running virt-manager from the desktop entry. Turns out, I need root access for it to work. In my previous setup with Fedora GNOME, I would simply get a password prompt with polkit-gnome. Running it in the terminal without root gives me the No Polkit Authentication error after it fails.&#xA;Why do I get the &amp;ldquo;No Polkit Authentication Agent&amp;rdquo; error?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Lid Close Behaviour On Ubuntu and Fedora</title>
      <link>https://lapjo.com/posts/change-lid-close-behaviour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 09:18:09 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lapjo.com/posts/change-lid-close-behaviour/</guid>
      <description>Change suspend on lid close on linux Default behaviour On most linux distributions the default behaviour is that when you close you laptop lid the computer will suspend all processes in order to save power. This is very useful as it reduces battery usage incase you unknowingly forgot to turn off your computer before a long trip or in any other situation.&#xA;But There are situations where you will want this behaviour changed so that you can tasks running with the lid closed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>the ultimate ncmpcpp config, for the best cli-based music player</title>
      <link>https://lapjo.com/posts/ncmpcpp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 20:00:20 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lapjo.com/posts/ncmpcpp/</guid>
      <description>Introduction ncmpcpp is a frontend for Music Player Daemon (MPD). MPD is a music player server that plays and organises audio files, playlists, etc. to interact (in a user friendly manner) with MPD we need a client application and ncmpcpp is one of these application. ncmpcpp is a fork of ncmpc that comes with many more features including but not limited to visualizer, tag editor, playlist editor, lyrics display and download.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
