<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech and opensource for you. on Lapjo</title>
    <link>https://lapjo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech and opensource for you. on Lapjo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 06:19:23 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lapjo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lost Memories</title>
      <link>https://lapjo.com/posts/lost_memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 06:19:23 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lapjo.com/posts/lost_memories/</guid>
      <description>2014, 14 year old me to my brother: remember we used to play space chimp on ps2?. He had no recallection of it whatsoever, infact none of my 3 older brothers remembered ever owning the game.
I am fairly certain to this day that we infact played it.
I&amp;rsquo;m sure this hasn&amp;rsquo;t only happened to me. Is there a word for it?, are there publications explaining or atleast trying to explain this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about a youtuber?</title>
      <link>https://lapjo.com/posts/direction_of_this/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 16:23:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lapjo.com/posts/direction_of_this/</guid>
      <description>I have been watching youtube videos from creator luke smith on youtube and have noticed that he will sometimes randomly not post anything for really long periods -a whole year.
It is actually quite interesting to me because I only ever notice a long time he actually posting which is not really the same with other creators and it&amp;rsquo;s led to go back and watch some of he&amp;rsquo;s content to understand why and I don&amp;rsquo;t actually understand why till now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Lid Close Behaviour On Ubuntu and Fedora</title>
      <link>https://lapjo.com/posts/change-lid-close-behaviour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 09:18:09 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lapjo.com/posts/change-lid-close-behaviour/</guid>
      <description>Default behaviour On most linux distributions the default behaviour is that when you close you laptop lid the computer will suspended all processes inorder to save power.
This is very useful as it reduces battery usage incase you unknowingly forgot to turn off your computer before a long trip or in any other situation.
But There are situations where you will want this behaviour changed so that you can tasks running with the lid closed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the ultimate ncmpcpp config, for the best cli-based music player</title>
      <link>https://lapjo.com/posts/ncmpcpp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 20:00:20 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lapjo.com/posts/ncmpcpp/</guid>
      <description>Introduction ncmpcpp is a frontend for Music Player Daemon (MPD). MPD is a music player server that plays and organises audio files, playlists, etc. to interact (in a user friendly manner) with MPD we need a client application and ncmpcpp is one of these application. ncmpcpp is a fork of ncmpc that comes with many more features including but not limited to visualizer, tag editor, playlist editor, lyrics display and download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is lapjo? or what is lapjo.com</title>
      <link>https://lapjo.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lapjo.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m lapjo and this is my blog.
the goal is to write whatever I feel like on a given day, it could be a how to, a poem, random blubberings, anything.
who I am is not particularly important, but I hope what I write will entertain or at the bare minimum bore you.
As I&amp;rsquo;d rather you remember my article as the one that bored you to death, let my legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
